<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
	<name>Initial Conditions #1: Subsistence</name>
	<author>Tammabanana</author>
	<targetVersion>0.16.1386</targetVersion>
	<description>Who needs winter clothes and food preservation - the first thing you do when you're stranded in the wilderness is set up a research station and stick your head in those papers and calculations, amirite?
	
	This mod adds a few items/recipes that will allow a settlement to establish itself at a very basic level without having to race up a tech tree or build All The Things. (I'm looking at you, tribal scenarios.)
	
	Features:
	
	* Smoked meat; a smokepit for small batches, and a more resource-intensive smokehouse for large batches.
	* Harvestable dandelions. (Edible, yo.) Greens don't store well, and you'd have to pick a lot to survive on them - but it's an option.
	* Recipes for making 5x simple/fine meals simultaneously.
	* Butchering allowed at the crafting spot, albeit more slowly.
	* Patch different types of leathers together at the crafting spot.
	* Smash chunks to get blocks, albeit much more slowly and for half the yield.
	* Wild haygrass, with which straw floors and rush bedding can be made.
	* Rough stone floors that use fewer stone blocks, but have no beauty.
	* Rough wood floors that use slightly less wood and have no beauty (and actually look rough); overwrite vanilla wood floors to use more wood and have more beauty.
	* "Worked earth" floors. This provides a smaller fertility boost than some other Tilled Soil variations - better than soil, but not as good as rich soil.
	* Makeable at the crafting spot: desert robes and head wraps for heat waves; fur coats and hats for the winter.
	
	Credits for original work (I've made edits to nearly everything):
	
	From fairly open mods; see links for original permissions/licenses:	
	* Smokehouse by Panggul_mas, https://ludeon.com/forums/index.php?topic=20387.0
	* Stone, wood, and straw floors by Telkir, https://ludeon.com/forums/index.php?topic=4373.0
	* Tilled Soil by Sam_, https://ludeon.com/forums/index.php?topic=5509.0
	* Double Sleeping Spot by TrueDestroyer, https://ludeon.com/forums/index.php?topic=26249.0
	
	Used with permission:
	* FashionRIMsta by Spoonshortage, Nackblad, and Shinzy, https://ludeon.com/forums/index.php?topic=24432.0
	
	</description>
</ModMetaData>
